gogetspace.com 2014-04-26

# Privacy policy : GoGetSpace

## Privacy Policy

### Collected Information

When you sign up for service with Gogetspace Web Hosting, we collect personal information from you including your name, e-mail address, billing address, security question (and answer), credit card or other payment information, and a password. We may also collect the URL from which you linked into our site, your IP address, and your browser type and version, all of which are collected in an anonymous manner without being linked to any of your personal information. 

### Use of Customer Information

Customer privacy is something we take very seriously at Gogetspace. We do not sell or disseminate (except in cases where required to by law enforcement agencies) the personal information of our customers to any parties outside of Gogetspace or its subsdiary companies, for any purpose other than communicating messages provided by Gogetspace. We use customer information for the purposes of creating and maintaining individual customer accounts, contacting customers in case of problems with their account(s), sending personal information, for statistical purposes, to administer our systems, to conduct surveys, to administer drawings or contests, to provide product and marketing updates, and to provide technical support. 

Gogetspace may engage with companies or agencies that may come in contact with some customer data only in cases where that access is required to support Gogetspace’s own goals and initiatives. Some optional partner offers and services may require customer information to be provided to third parties as a necessary part of establishing service with them. Please note that the contact information that you provide to us is used to register your domain name and is, by the very nature of the domain registration system, available for public viewing in many places on the Internet via the use of the ‘whois’ tool. 

### Whois Privacy Services

Whois Privacy as offered by Gogetspace does not act as a shield from legal liability in conjunction with Domain Registration. In order to preserve neutrality in disputes between 3rd parties and domain registrants, Gogetspace will act in accordance with ICANN Registrar Accreditation agreement section 3.7.7.3 upon receipt of actionable evidence of illegal activity. This means that identifying information will be provided to law enforcement and officials of the court including attorneys as situations require in order preserving Gogetspace’s neutrality in any litigation.
